





Senior Software Engineer seeking roles in Software Development, Application Programming, Application Maintenance, Project Management, Requirement Analysis, Solution Architecture, Core Java, Hibernate, JDBC, Spring Boot, Micro services, Restful Web Services



Total Experience: 6 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Electronics/Telecommunication]

Current Designation: Senior Software Engineer -Java/J2EE

Current Company: HCL

Current Location: Hyderabad / Secunderabad

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Chennai, Hyderabad Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Role: Team Lead/Tech Lead

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: Senior Software Engineer, Tech Lead, Software Development, Application Programming, Application Maintenance, Project Management, Requirement Analysis, Solution Architecture, Core Java, Hibernate, JDBC, Spring Boot, Mcro services, Restful Web Services

Verified : Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 19-Jan-21

Last Modified: 19-Jan-21

Jump to Section

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

Summary

Having 6.3 years of experience in Java / J2EE Technologies, Worked on Bootstrap, Jquery, Angular JS, Angular6, Angular material, Core Java, Java8, JSP, Servlets, Spring, Spring boot, Spring cloud, Mcro services, Hibernate, mysql in Windows Environment, especially on Web Applications. Looking for a challenging employment opportunity in the areas of Angular and Java/J2EE.

Work Experience

- HCL as Senior Software Engineer -Java/J2EE Sep 2018 to Till Date
- Fluentgrid Limited as Software Engineer Sep 2015 to Sep 2018
- Vedams Software Solutions India Pvt Ltd as Software Engineer May 2014 to Sep 2015

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Electronics/Telecommunication) from JNTU College of Engineering, Hyderabad in 2010

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
CORE JAVA	
Hibernate	
JDBC	
Spring	
spring boot	



Important

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

opg
MICRO SERVICES
RESTful Web Services
Junit and Mockito
HTML, CSS, Bootstrap
Angularjs
JQUERY
Eclipse, SonarQube
maven, svn
GIT, VSCode
MySQL

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Telugu				

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.